Mss.B.W564
American Philosophical Society
- II. University of Texas Correspondence and Files, 1976-2006 (Box 34-71)
  - Banerji, S., 1977 (Box 35)
  - Banks, Leslie, 1984-1987 (Box 35)
  - Banna, Ing. Pietro, 1979 (Box 35)
  - Barker, Gerald, 1980 (Box 35)
  - Barlow, John S., 1976-1978 (Box 35)
  - Barnes, Harry G., Jr., 1984 (Box 35)
    -- See also Series II: Rostow, Elspeth
  - Barnothy, Jeno M., 1984 (Box 35)
  - Barr, E. Scott, 1982-1987, n.d. (Box 35)
  - Barr, Jane S. (Mrs. Robert W.), 1979 (Box 35)
  - Barrow, John D., 1976-1985 (Box 35)
    -- See also Series II: Tipler, Frank J.
  - Barschall, Henry Herman, 1979-1987, n.d. (Box 35)
  - Bartell, Larry S., 1978-1984 (Box 35)
    -- See also Series II: Sarfatti, Jack (1980)
  - Bass, Henry E., 1977 (Box 35)
  - Bastin, Ted, 1976-1979 (Box 35)
    Kilmister, Clyde W.; Noyes, H. Pierre. -- See also Series II: Noyes, H. Pierre
  - Battelle Memorial Institute, 1977-1983 (Box 35)
    Batch, John M.; Fawcett, Sherwood L. -- See also Series II: Goldstein, Allan L.; Lawrence Livermore Laboratory
  - Bauer, Henry H., 1983 (Box 35)
  - Bay, Austin, 1979 (Box 35)
    Omni
  - Bayless, James, 1981-1986 (Box 35)
  - Baym, Gordon, 1982 (Box 35)
  - Bearden, Thomas E., 1977 (Box 35)
  - Becker, Dean B., III, 1983 (Box 35)
  - Bedrij, Orest J., 1977 (Box 35)
  - Bekenstein, Jacob D., 1976-1987 (Box 35)
  - Belinfante, Frederik J., 1976-1980 (Box 35)
  - Belinsky, Volodja, 1977-1978 (Box 35)
  - Bell, John, 1976-1978 (Box 35)
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories, Inc., 1979 (Box 35)
  - Bellingham, Tom McDavid, 1976 (Box 35)
  - BenDaniel, David J., 1984 (Box 35)
  - Benedict, Manson, 1982 (Box 35)
  - Bengtson, Roger, 1984-1988 (Box 35)
    -- See also Series II: Matzner, Richard A.
  - Benioff, Paul A., 1977 (Box 35)
    Deutsch, David
  - Bennett, Charles, 1981-1985 (Box 35)
  - Bentley, Ruth C., 1977-1982, n.d. (Box 35)
  - Berard, Marcel, 1977 (Box 36)
  - Berdjis, Fazlollah, 1984 (Box 36)
  - Berger, Beverly Kobre, 1977 (Box 36)
  - Berger, Kathryn G., 1983 (Box 36)
  - Berger, Melvin S., 1978 (Box 36)
  - Bergson and Modern Science: An Interdisciplinary Conference, 1983 (Box 36)
  - Bernardini, Ghilberto, 1977 (Box 36)
  - Bernstein, Jeremy, 1985 (Box 36)
  - Bernstein, Richard B., 1977 (Box 36)
  - Berry, Adrian, 1977 (Box 36)
  - Berry, Michael V., 1983-1987 (Box 36)
  - Bers, Lipman, 1978 (Box 36)
  - Bertoldi, Philip E., 1980 (Box 36)
  - Bertotti, Bruno, 1977-1987 (Box 36)
  - Bethe, Hans A., 1977-1983 (Box 36)
    -- See also Series II: Teller, Edward; Union of Concerned Scientists
  - Beven, Terry P., 1977 (Box 36)
  - Bicak, Jiri, 1978 (Box 36)
  - Biedenharn, Lawrence C., 1981-1985 (Box 36)
  - Bing, R. H., 1979-1983 (Box 36)
    -- See also Series II: Lewis, Albert C.
  - Bishop, Robert C., 1983-1986 (Box 36)
  - Bishop, Roy L., 1981, n.d. (Box 36)
    -- See also Series II: Sky and Telescope
  - Basil Blackwell Ltd., 1986 (Box 36)
  - Blaedel, Niels, 1984-1985 (Box 36)
  - Bleick, William E., 1984 (Box 36)
  - Block, Edward M., 1979 (Box 36)
  - Blumberg, Roland K., 1978-1988 (Box 36)
    Blumberg, Jane
  - Blumberg, Stanley A., 1984-1987 (Box 36)
    -- See also Series II: Teller, Edward
  - Bocko, Mark F., 1983-1984 (Box 36)
  - Bohm, Arno, 1977-1986 (Box 36)
    -- See also Series II: Group Theory and Fundamental Physics Foundation
  - Bohm, David J., 1976-1985 (Box 36)
    Hiley, Basil J.; Peat, F. David
  - Bohr, Aage, 1977-1986 (Box 36)
    Winther, Aage (1981)
  - Bohr, Henrik G., 1982-1983 (Box 36)
  - Bohr, Margrethe (Mrs. Niels), 1981-1985 (Box 36)
  - Bohr, Marietta (Mrs. Aage), n.d. (Box 36)
    Wheeler, Janette; Niels Bohr Institute. See also Series II: Niels Bohr Institute
  - Bolling, Imogene Adams (Mrs. William), 1984 (Box 36)
    Bolling, William
  - Bolling, William, 1980-1984 (Box 36)
    See also Series II: Bolling, Imogene Adams
  - Bordoni, Manlio, 1980 (Box 36)
  - Boris, Jay Paul, 1979 (Box 36)
  - Born, Gustav V. R., 1980-1982 (Box 36)
    Harrington, Claire
  - Bose Institute of Physical Sciences, 1978-1983 (Box 36)
  - Bowen, William G., 1981 (Box 36)
    -- See also Series II: Princeton University, Department of Physics, Advisory Council ([1978-1979], 1982-1983)
  - Boyer, Robert E., 1982-1986 (Box 36)
  - Boynton, Paul, 1977 (Box 36)
  - Braginsky, Vladimir B., 1976-1984 (Box 36)
  - Braithwaite, Wilfred J., 1977-1979 (Box 36)
  - Bramley, Jenny E., 1985 (Box 36)
  - Brans, Carl, 1978-1979 (Box 36)
  - Brecher, Kenneth, 1979-1986 (Box 36)
  - Breit, Gregory, 1976-1979 (Box 37)
    -- See also Series II: Breit, Marjorie MacDill; Cox, Richard T.
  - Breit, Marjorie MacDill (Mrs. Gregory), 1979-1982 (Box 37)
    Breit, Gregory
  - Bressan, Oscar J., 1978 (Box 37)
  - Brewer, Jess H., 1986 (Box 37)
  - Brewin, Leo, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Brian, Denis, 1981-1985 (Box 37)
    Rhine, J. B.
  - Bridges, Connie, 1978 (Box 37)
  - Brier, Bob, 1985 (Box 37)
  - Brill, Dieter R., 1976-1987 (Box 37)
  - Brisson, D. W., 1976-1979 (Box 37)
  - British Association for the Advancement of Science, 1981 (Box 37)
    Dicke, R[obert] H.; Dirac, P. A. M.; Runcorn, S. K[eith]
  - British Broadcasting Corp. TV, 1978-1979 (Box 37)
    Calder, Nigel
  - Brokaw, R. Miriam, 1984-1985 (Box 37)
  - Bromley, Allan, 1977, 1985 (Box 37)
  - Bronk, Burt V., 1978-1979 (Box 37)
  - Brown, Gerald, 1977 (Box 37)
  - Brown, John David, 1981-1986 (Box 37)
  - Brown, Laurie M., 1978 (Box 37)
  - Brown, Lowell S., 1976-1977 (Box 37)
  - Brown, Martin R., 1977-1978, n.d. (Box 37)
  - Brown, Salley E., 1978-1979 (Box 37)
  - Broyles, Arthur A., 1979-1985 (Box 37)
  - Brudner, Harvey J., 1979 (Box 37)
  - Brush, Stephen G., 1978-1983 (Box 37)
  - Bryson, David, 1986 (Box 37)
  - Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists, 1979 (Box 37)
  - Bunge, Mario, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Burbidge, E. Margaret, 1984-1985 (Box 37)
  - Burgess, Clifford P. (Box 37)
  - Burk, Creighton, 1978 (Box 37)
    Runcorn, S. Keith
  - Burkhardt, Frederick H., 1978, 1985 (Box 37)
  - Burns, Marshall, 1982-1987 (Box 37)
  - Burzlaff, Jurgen, 1978 (Box 37)
  - Busch, Paul, 1983-1984 (Box 37)
  - Bussard, Robert W., 1977-1982 (Box 37)
  - Bussey, D. J., 1985 (Box 37)
  - Cabibbo, Nicola, 1982-1985 (Box 37)
  - Cahill, Kevin, 1977-1978 (Box 37)
  - Caianiello, Eduardo R., 1976-1986, n.d. (Box 37)
  - Calder, Nigel, 1977-1979 (Box 37)
    -- See also Series II: British Broadcasting Corp. TV
  - Calhoun, John B., 1977 (Box 37)
  - California Institute of Technology, 1977 (Box 37)
  - California State University, 1986 (Box 37)
  - Camber, Bruce, 1979 (Box 37)
  - Campbell, Donald, 1978 (Box 37)
  - Canadian Journal of Physics, 1977-1980 (Box 37)
  - Cantor, Judi, 1977-1980 (Box 37)
  - Cantor, Murray, 1980-1981 (Box 37)
  - Canuto, Vittorio, 1985 (Box 37)
  - Career Aptitude Testing, Ltd., 1978 (Box 38)
  - Careri, Giorgio, 1985 (Box 38)
  - Carey, S. Warren, 1980 (Box 38)
  - Carlip, Steven, 1985 (Box 38)
  - Carmeli, Moshe, 1976-1984 (Box 38)
  - Carr, Bernard J., 1979 (Box 38)
  - Carroll, John B., 1978 (Box 38)
  - Carstoiu, John, 1979-1986 (Box 38)
  - Carter, Brandon, 1977-1978 (Box 38)
  - Carter, Neal E., 1987 (Box 38)
  - Cartier, Joan F., 1982 (Box 38)
  - Cartier, Pierre, 1984 (Box 38)
  - Casati, G., 1984 (Box 38)
  - Casimir, Heinrich Brugt Gerhard, 1978, 1985 (Box 38)
  - Cassidy, David C., 1981 (Box 38)
  - Casson, Andrew John, 1981 (Box 38)
  - Castagnino, Mario A., 1986 (Box 38)
  - Castellanos, Dario, 1980-1982 (Box 38)
  - Castillo, Anthony, 1977-1980 (Box 38)
  - Caves, Carlton M., [1977]-1987 (Box 38)
  - Cazenave, Michel, 1984 (Box 38)
  - Ceapa, Alexandre, 1977-1978 (Box 38)
  - Centrella, Joan M., 1977-1986 (Box 38)
  - Cetkovic, Dragoljub, 1980-1987 (Box 38)
  - Chaisson, Eric J., 1977 (Box 38)
  - Chako, Nick, 1985, n.d. (Box 38)
  - Chandler, Susan M., 1977-1984 (Box 38)
    Pierce, John R.
  - Chandasekhar, Subrahmanyan, 1978-1983 (Box 38)
  - Chang, Wen-Yu, 1979-1985 (Box 38)
  - Chen, K. Wendell, 1978 (Box 38)
  - Chiao, Raymond Yu, 1976-1985, n.d. (Box 38)
    -- See also Series II: DeWitt, Bryce S.
  - China-U.S. Physics Examination and Application (CUSPEA) Program, 1980-1987; 2.0 folders (Box 38)
    Lee, Tsung Dao
  - Chiu, Charles, 1980 (Box 38)
  - Chizmarik, Joseph J., 1976-1983 (Box 38)
  - Choquet-Bruhat, Yvonne, 1978-1985 (Box 39)
  - Christensen, Steven M., 1976-1982 (Box 39)
    DeWitt, Bryce
  - Christian Science Monitor (Box 39)
    Buckmaster, Henrietta
  - Christodoulou, Demetrios, 1976-1984 (Box 39)
  - Christodoulou, Lambros, 1979 (Box 39)
  - Christy, James W., 1979 (Box 39)
    Josties, F. Jerzy
  - Chrzanowski, Paul, 1977 (Box 39)
  - Chudnovsky, David, 1981, n.d. (Box 39)
    -- See also Series II: International Conference in Honor of Andrei Sakharov; Sakharov, Andrei (1980-1981)
  - Chudnovsky, Gregory, 1981 (Box 39)
  - Ciraolo, Giovanni, 1978 (Box 39)
  - Citadel, 1985-1986 (Box 39)
  - Clarendon Press, 1978 (Box 39)
  - Clark, Adrian V., 1978 (Box 39)
  - Clark, John W., 1978-1986 (Box 39)
    Feenberg, Eugene
  - Clarke, C. J .S., 1980 (Box 39)
  - Claudet, Sonia (Mrs. Claudio Teitelboim), 1979-1980 (Box 39)
  - Clayton, D. D., 1980 (Box 39)
  - Clendenning, Lester, 1978 (Box 39)
  - Cleveland State Commmunity College, 1979 (Box 39)
  - Coalition for the Strategic Defense Initiative, 1986 (Box 39)
  - Cocke, W. J[ohn], 1982 (Box 39)
  - Cohen, Avner, 1976-1979 (Box 39)
  - Cohen, E. G. D., 1978 (Box 39)
  - Cohen, Jeffrey M., 1979-1985 (Box 39)
  - Cohn, Jack, 1979 (Box 39)
  - Coker, William Rory, 1978-1986 (Box 39)
  - Collier, John S., 1978-1979 (Box 39)
  - Collins, Christopher Barry, 1977-1984 (Box 39)
  - Collins, R. Eugene, 1978-1980 (Box 39)
  - Colloque International Pluridisciplinaire sur le Rôle de l'Esprit en Science, 1982-1983 (Box 39)
  - Columbus School for Girls, 1982 (Box 39)
  - Comstock Club, Inc., 1979-1981 (Box 39)
  - Conversation with John Wheeler. UTmost: The Student Magazine of the University of Texas. Winter, 1981 (Box 39)
  - Cooper, Karen Bond, 1984 (Box 39)
  - Coppi, Bruno, 1978 (Box 39)
  - Corben, Bert, 1978 (Box 39)
  - Corelli, John C., 1977 (Box 39)
  - Cosmic Search, 1978-1979 (Box 39)
    Kraus, John
  - Courvoisier, Jean-Claude, 1978-1985 (Box 39)
  - Courvoisier, Thierry J.-L., 1976-1984 (Box 39)
  - Cox, Richard T., 1976-1979 (Box 39)
  - Cowan-Reed, Betty, 1987 (Box 39)
    Cowan, Clyde
  - Cramer, John G., 1978-1984 (Box 39)
  - Cranberg, Lawrence, 1977-1983 (Box 39)
    American Physical Society; Union of Concerned Scientists
  - Crane, P. W., 1980 (Box 39)
  - Crawford, John David, 1977-1980 (Box 39)
  - Crawley, Frank E., 1981 (Box 39)
  - Crelinstein, Jeffrey, 1981 (Box 39)
  - Critchfield, Charles L., 1977 (Box 39)
  - Critchley, R., 1980 (Box 39)
  - Cronin, James W., 1976-1980 (Box 39)
    Fitch, [Val L.]
  - Cunningham, William H., 1985-1986 (Box 39)
  - Curtis, Geoffrey Edward, 1976-1977 (Box 39)
  - Damgaard, Poul Henrik, 1977 (Box 39)
  - Damiris, Nicholas, 1985 (Box 39)
  - Damour, Thibaut, 1976-1977 (Box 39)
  - Danescu, Dan Petru, 1977-1978 (Box 39)
  - Daniel, James W., 1978 (Box 39)
  - Darsey, Jerry A., 1987 (Box 39)
  - Datta, Bidyut Kumar, 1980-1983 (Box 39)
  - Daugherty, Ralph, 1979 (Box 39)
  - Davenport, Tom Forest III, 1976 (Box 39)
  - Davies, Barbara, 1982 (Box 39)
  - Davies, Paul C. W., 1978-1986 (Box 39)
  - Davies, Shannon Melinda, 1982-1986 (Box 39)
    Stott, William M.
  - Davis, Lincoln Ross, 1979-1981 (Box 39)
  - Davis, Raymond, Jr., 1978, 1982 (Box 39)
  - Davis, T. Michael, 1976-1977 (Box 39)
  - De, Bibhas R., 1978 (Box 40)
  - DeAlwis, Senarath Prashanta, 1986 (Box 40)
  - Dean, William, 1981-1984 (Box 40, Box OS1)
  - Debelack, Andrew S., 1984-1985 (Box 40)
  - Debever, Robert, 1977-1985 (Box 40)
  - DeCampli, William Michael, 1980 (Box 40)
  - Decker, R. David, Jr., 1979 (Box 40)
  - DeFacio, B., 1978-1979 (Box 40)
    Retzloff, D.
  - de Felice, Fernando, 1976-1980 (Box 40)
  - di Finis, Francesco, 1976-1979 (Box 40)
  - DeGracia, Donald J., 1986-1987 (Box 40)
  - de Groot, Sybren R., 1979 (Box 40)
  - Dehmelt, Hans, 1986 (Box 40)
  - Delbruck, Max, 1976, 1981 (Box 40)
  - Demaret, Jacques, 1979-1986, n.d. (Box 40)
  - De Marchi, Carla, 1977 (Box 40)
  - De Martini, Francesco, 1983-1985 (Box 40)
  - Demianski, Marek, 1980-1988, n.d. (Box 40)
  - Dennett, Daniel C., 1976-1977 (Box 40)
  - Deodikar, G. B., 1976-1977 (Box 40)
    Maharashtra Association for the Cultivation of Science
  - DePalma, Bruce E., 1977 (Box 40)
  - Deser, Stanley, 1982 (Box 40)
  - DeSieno, Robert P., 1976-1977 (Box 40)
  - d'Espagnat, Bernard, 1976-1985 (Box 40)
  - Deutsch, David, 1976-1987; 2.0 folders (Box 40)
    -- See also Series II: Benioff, Paul A.
    - Folder #1, 1976-1984 (Box 40)
    - Folder #2, 1985-1987 (Box 40)
  - deVaucouleurs, Gerard Henri, 1980-1982 (Box 40)
  - Devons, Sam, 1983 (Box 40)
  - de Wette, Frederik Willem, 1980, 1983 (Box 40)
  - DeWitt, Bryce S., 1977-1988 (Box 40)
    Chiao, Raymond; Sherwin, Mark. -- See also Series II: Christensen, Steven M.; Everett, Hugh III
  - DeWitt-Morette, Cecile, 1978-1984 (Box 40)
  - Diamond, Richard, 1983 (Box 41)
  - Diaz Montoya, Alvaro Hernan, 1981-1985 (Box 41)
  - Dicke, Robert H., 1976-1986 (Box 41)
    -- See also Series II: British Association for the Advancement of Science
  - Dicus, Duane, 1982 (Box 41)
  - Dillon, Wilton Sterling, 1976 (Box 41)
  - Dirac, M[anci] (Mrs. Paul A. M.), 1984 (Box 41)
  - Dirac, Paul A. M., 1978-1981 (Box 41)
    -- See also Series II: British Association for the Advancement of Science; Dyson, Freeman J. (1979); Prime, Alfred C. -- See also Series IV: "Electron Pair Theory: Unfinished Tower"
  - Discovery Hall, 1984 (Box 41)
    Turner, Jack S.
  - Dockx, S., 1977 (Box 41)
  - Dollard, John Day, 1977, 1987-1988 (Box 41)
  - Dombroski, Mike, 1979 (Box 41)
  - Donovan, Thomas A., 1978 (Box 41)
  - Dougherty, Ralph C., 1977-1980 (Box 41)
  - Doughty, Noel, 1979, n.d. (Box 41)
  - Down, David, 1981-1985 (Box 41)
  - Downes, Philip, 1976 (Box 41)
    Hawking, Stephen W.
  - Drell, Sidney D., 1978-1984 (Box 41)
    -- See also Series II: Internaitonal Conference in Honor of Andrei Sakharov; Sakharov, Andrei (1982, 1984)
  - Dresden, Max, 1983 (Box 41)
  - Drost-Hansen, W., 1982 (Box 41)
  - Dubisch, Russell, 1978 (Box 41)
  - Duff, Michael J., 1976-1984 (Box 41)
  - Dunnam, Sam E., 1980-1986 (Box 41)
  - Dunnam, Valerie, 1978 (Box 41)
  - E. I. du Pont de Nemours and Co., 1977-1980 (Box 41)
    Lorenz, C. Edward; Simmons, Howard [E.]
  - Durr, Hans Peter, 1979-1981, n.d. (Box 41)
  - Duvall, George E., 1977 (Box 41)
  - Dykema, Pieter Geer, 1977, 1980 (Box 41)
  - Dyson, Freeman J., 1979-1986 (Box 41)
    Cooper, [Leon] (1979); Dirac, P. A. M. (1979); Field, [?] (1979); Laughton, [?] (1979); Ne'eman, [Yuval] (1979); Ostriker, [?] (1979); Segre, [Emilio] (1979); Wigner, [Eugene P.] (1979)
  - Eardley, Douglas M., 1977 (Box 41)
  - East-West Philosophy Encounter, 1983 (Box 41)
  - Eastern Theoretical Physics Conference, 1976-1977 (Box 41)
  - Eccles, John C. (Sir), 1977-1985 (Box 41)
  - Ecklin, John W., 1976-1979 (Box 41)
  - Edwards, Gregg, 1978 (Box 41)
  - Eglin, James M., 1986 (Box 41)
  - Ehlers, Jurgen, 1978, 1985 (Box 41)
    Wheeler, J. Craig
  - Eigen, Manfred, 1985 (Box 41)
  - Einstein Papers, 1977-1988; 7.0 folders (Box 41-42)
    Einstein, A[lbert] (27 Sept. 1977); Holton, Gerald (1984); Nathan, Otto (1978-1982); Princeton University Press (1977-1987); Stachel, John (1977-1986); Stromberg, Gustaf (27 Sept. 1977); Yaron, Reuven (1983-1984)
    - Folders #1-2, 1977 (Box 41)
    - Folder #3, 1978 (Box 41)
    - Folder #4, 1979-1981 (Box 42)
    - Folders #5-6, 1982 (Box 42)
    - Folder #7, 1983-1988 (Box 42)
  - Einstein Foundation International, 1983 (Box 42)
  - Elkana, Yehuda, 1979-1988 (Box 42)
  - Ellis, George F. R., 1981-1984 (Box 42)
  - Elsasser, Walter M., 1984-1987 (Box 42)
  - Elton, Lewis, 1986 (Box 42)
  - Elton, Sam, 1979 (Box 42)
  - Emami, Iraj, 1978-1986 (Box 42)
  - Emch, Gerard G., 1985 (Box 42)
  - Encyclopedia Britannica, Inc., 1981-1984 (Box 42)
  - Encyclopedia of the Twentieth Century, 1980 (Box 42)
  - Engineering Design Graphics Journal, 1976-1977 (Box 42)
    DeJong, Paul S.
  - Eringer, Robert H., 1978 (Box 42)
  - Ern, Vladimiro, 1978 (Box 42)
  - Ernst, Fred, 1978 (Box 42)
  - Erskine, James L., 1977-1978 (Box 42)
  - Estabrook, Frank B., 1978-1981 (Box 42)
  - Evans, David S., 1986 (Box 42)
  - Everett, Hugh III, 1977-1979 (Box 42)
    DeWitt, Bryce S.
  - Everitt, C. W. Francis, 1977-1988, n.d. (Box 42)
    Fairbank, William H.; NASA (National Aeronautics and Space Administration); United States, Office of Science and Technology Policy
  - Eyink, Gregory L., 1986 (Box 42)
  - Fagg, Lawrence W., 1976, 1987 (Box 42)
  - Fairbank, William M., 1982-1983 (Box 42)
    -- See also Series II: Everitt, C. W. Francis
  - Faller, James E., 1986 (Box 43)
  - Fang, Li Zhi, 1980-1987 (Box 43)
  - Faris, Robert E. L., 1979 (Box 43)
  - Faris, William, 1977 (Box 43)
    -- See also Series II: Tiomno, Jayme
  - Farrington, Jeremiah A., 1978-1979 (Box 43)
  - Faulkner, John, 1977 (Box 43)
  - Federico, Peter J., 1976-1978 (Box 43)
  - Feibel, Werner, 1976-1977 (Box 43)
  - Feigenbaum, Mitchell, 1984 (Box 43)
    -- See also Series III: Mitchell Feigenbaum and Disorder
  - Feinberg, Gerald, 1981-1985 (Box 43)
  - Ferris, Timothy, 1976-1986 (Box 43)
  - Feshbach, Herman, 1986 (Box 43)
  - Feynman, Richard Phillips, 1977-1986 (Box 43)
  - Finck, Joseph Louis, 1976 (Box 43)
  - Fine, Leonard W., 1982 (Box 43)
  - Fink, Manfred, 1977-1985 (Box 43)
  - Finkbeiner, Ann, 1984 (Box 43)
  - Finkelstein, David, 1977-1985 (Box 43)
  - Finkelstein, Robert J., 1979 (Box 43)
  - Finnerty, William Patrick, 1977-1987 (Box 43)
  - Fireman, Ed L., 1976 (Box 43)
  - Fischbach, Ephraim, 1979, 1986 (Box 43)
  - Fischer, Arthur Elliot, 1978-1985 (Box 43)
  - Fischetti, Massimo (Max), 1979 (Box 43)
  - Fisher, Michael Ellis, 1985-1986 (Box 43)
  - Fitch, Val Logsdon, 1976-1980 (Box 43)
    Cronin, James W.; Shenstone, Allen G. -- See also Series II: Cronin, James W. (1978); Princeton University, Department of Physics, Advisory Council (1977-1979)
  - Fitzpatrick, Gerald L., 1983-1986 (Box 43)
  - Fitzwilliam, Jim, 1977 (Box 43)
  - Flawn, Peter T., 1978-1980 (Box 43)
    -- See also Series II: King, Robert D.; University of Texas at Austin
  - Fleming, Ed, 1979 (Box 43)
  - Fleming, Russell, Jr., 1976-1977 (Box 43)
  - Flerov, Georgy N., 1977-1983 (Box 43)
  - Folkers, Karl, 1980-1983 (Box 43)
    John D. and Catherine T. MacArthur Foundation
  - Follesdal, Dagfinn, 1985-1986 (Box 43)
    Causey, Robert L.
  - Fong, Peter, 1981 (Box 43)
  - Fonken, Gerhard, 1985 (Box 43)
  - Ford, Joseph, 1984 (Box 43)
  - Ford, Kenneth W., 1978-1986 (Box 43)
    -- See also Series II: Alley, Reuben E., Jr.
  - Ford, Lawrence Howard, 1976-1981 (Box 43)
  - Forman, Paul, 1979-1981 (Box 43)
    Peierls, Rudolf
  - Forrest, David V., 1977 (Box 43)
  - Fosdick, Dorothy, 1981 (Box 43)
    -- See also Series II: Henry M. Jackson Foundation
  - Foss, Donald J., 1979, n.d. (Box 43)
  - Foudas, Constantinos, 1984-1985 (Box 43)
  - Foundations of Physics, 1984-1987 (Box 43)
    van der Merwe, Alwyn. -- See also Series II: Mielke, Eckehard W. (1984)
  - Fowler, Joe L., 1977 (Box 43)
  - Fowler, William A., 1983-1984 (Box 43)
  - Francaviglia, Mauro, 1976-1985, n.d. (Box 44)
  - Frankel, Theodore, 1979 (Box 44)
  - Fraser, John T., 1979-1982, n.d. (Box 44)
  - Frauenfelder, Hans, 1979-1981 (Box 44)
  - Frautschi, Steven C., 1977 (Box 44)
  - Fredonia State University College, 1981 (Box 44)
  - W. H. Freeman and Co., Publishers, 1978-1986 (Box 44)
    Misner, Charles W. (1979-1980); Renz, Peter; Thorne, Kip S. (1979-1980). -- See also Series II: Sardelis, D. A.; Taylor, Edwin F.; Thorne, Kip S.
  - French, [A. P.], 1985 (Box 44)
    -- See also Series II: International Commission on Physics Education
  - Friedman, Harvey, 1987 (Box 44)
  - Friedman, Joel I., 1978-1980 (Box 44)
  - Frieman, Edward, 1984 (Box 44)
  - Frieman, Joshua, 1985 (Box 44)
  - Frisch, Otto Robert, 1978 (Box 44)
  - Froman, Nanny, 1978 (Box 44)
  - Frombold, Lothar, [1985] (Box 44)
  - Fry, Edward S., 1977-1986, n.d. (Box 44)
  - Frye, Roland Mushat, 1980-1983 (Box 44)
  - Fuchs, Christopher, 1984-1985 (Box 44)
  - Fuller, Robert W., 1976-1986 (Box 44)
  - Fulling, Stephen Albert, 1976-1977 (Box 44)
  - Fundamental Aspects of Quantum Theory (Conference), 1984-1985 (Box 44)
  - Futterman, John Arthur Hardt, 1977-1981 (Box 44)
  - Gabor, Ofer, 1981 (Box 44)
  - Gale, William A., 1977 (Box 44)
  - Gallagher, Anthony Martin, 1977-1979 (Box 44)
  - Gallimore, J. G., 1979 (Box 44)
  - Gal-Or, Ben, 1985 (Box 44)
  - Ganea, Ioan-Mihail, 1979 (Box 44)
  - Gardner, Martin, 1978-1986 (Box 44)
    -- See also Series II: Poundstone, William
  - Garrett, Beverly Jean, 1979-1980 (Box 44)
  - Garrison, Michael, 1980 (Box 44)
  - Garwin, Richard L., 1983 (Box 44)
  - Gautam, Sulaksh R. (Bingo), 1986 (Box 44)
  - Gavenda, David, 1987 (Box 44)
  - Gefwert, Christoffer, 1983-1986 (Box 44)
    -- See also Series II: Noyes, H. Pierre
  - Geheniau, Jules, 1979-1981 (Box 44)
  - Gelphman, Janet, 1980-1984, n.d. (Box 44)
  - General Relativity and Gravitation, 1977-1979 (Box 44)
    -- See also Series II: Sedov, Leonid I.
  - Gentry, Robert V., 1976, 1983 (Box 44)
  - Gerlach, Ulrich H., 1976-1986 (Box 44)
  - Geroch, Robert, 1976-1984 (Box 44)
  - Gerwin, Robert, 1979 (Box 44)
  - Gilbert, Field, 1982-1985, n.d. (Box 44)
  - Gilvarry, John J., 1978 (Box 44)
  - Gingerich, Owen, 1977-1979 (Box 44)
  - Glass, H. Bentley, 1979 (Box 44)
  - Glauber, Roy J., 1982 (Box 44)
  - Gleason, Andrew M., 1978-1979 (Box 44)
    Greenwood, Robert E.
  - Gleichauf, Paul H., 1985-1988 (Box 44)
    Klauder, John R.
  - Glikson, Andrew Y., 1979-1981 (Box 44)
  - Glimm, James, 1985-1986 (Box 44)
  - Glymour, Clark, 1977-1978 (Box 44)
  - Godart, Raphael, 1977 (Box 45)
  - Godfrey, Brendan Berry, 1985-1986 (Box 45)
  - Gold, Thomas, 1980-1984 (Box 45)
  - Goldberg, Joshua N., 1978-1979 (Box 45)
  - Goldberger, Marvin Leonard, 1976-1978 (Box 45)
  - Goldhaber, Gerson, 1981 (Box 45)
  - Goldhaber, Maurice, 1980-1981 (Box 45)
  - Goldhaber, [Trudy], 1978 (Box 45)
  - Goldman, Eric F., 1977 (Box 45)
  - Goldman, Itzhak, 1977 (Box 45)
  - Goldstein, Allan L., 1977-1978 (Box 45)
  - Goldstein, Harold, 1977-1978 (Box 45)
  - Goldstein, Jerome A., 1979 (Box 45)
  - Gomany, John, 1977 (Box 45)
  - Gombrich, E. H., 1978 (Box 45)
  - Gonshak, Irving, 1977 (Box 45)
  - Good, I. Jack, 1978-1986 (Box 45)
  - Goodfield, June, 1977 (Box 45)
  - Goodman, Nelson, 1979 (Box 45)
  - Gordon, Frederick B., 1977 (Box 45)
  - Gorelik, G. E., 1981 (Box 45)
  - Gorini, V., 1982 (Box 45)
  - Goudsmit, Samuel, 1978 (Box 45)
  - Gowdy, Robert H., 1976-1982 (Box 45)
  - Gowing, Margaret, 1978 (Box 45)
  - Grand Valley State Colleges, 1980 (Box 45)
  - Grasberger, William, 1984 (Box 45)
  - Graves, John C., 1982 (Box 45)
  - Gray, Reginald Irvan, 1978 (Box 45)
  - Green, Louis, 1981 (Box 45)
  - Green, Martin A., 1979 (Box 45)
  - Greenberg, Oscar Wallace, 1977-1978 (Box 45)
  - Greenstein, George, 1980 (Box 45)
  - Greenwood, Robert E., 1979, n.d. (Box 45)
    -- See also Series II: Gleason, Andrew M.; Lewis, Albert C.
  - Greisen, Kenneth, 1982 (Box 45)
    Colgate, Stirling
  - Gresky, Alan Tolstoy, 1977 (Box 45)
  - Greyber, Howard D., 1979-1986; 2.0 folders (Box 45)
    - Folder #1, 1979-1984 (Box 45)
    - Folder #2, 1985-1986 (Box 45)
  - Griboval, Paul, 1977 (Box 45)
  - Griffin, James J., 1979, 1986 (Box 45)
  - Griffy, Thomas, 1977-1981 (Box 45)
  - Grishchuk, Leonid P., 1978-1982 (Box 45)
  - Griswold, Erwin N., 1977-1980 (Box 45)
    Wright, Charles A.
  - Groenewold, Hilbrand J., 1978 (Box 45)
  - Group Theory and Fundamental Physics Foundation, 1976-1986 (Box 45)
    Bohm, Arno
  - Grove, Lloyd, 1979 (Box 45)
  - Gruber, Bruno, 1978 (Box 45)